[Music]
and from the skin shop
detroit michigan lightning
all right partner take the scumbag
downtown before the mexicans find him
and blow his ass away
i'm gonna keep you alive chico comprende
[Music]
so
[Applause]
[Music]
no
is that a bird hey
do you know what happened no
oh
[Music]
oh i get it when i say no
stuff blows up
cool
[Applause]
live from the nestle arena welcome to
the finals of the 1987
jazz fit championships representing the
body shop
from hollywood california flag
and from the skin shop detroit michigan
lightning
[Music]
[Applause]
so
[Music]
[Applause]
do
[Music]
so
[Applause]
[Music]
nobody likes you you girl well you're a
different color than me
and that's bad oh yeah well you dress
like a now hold on a second whoa
mr t never make fun of the way a man
dresses
weyman dresses is his business
remember that whether it's overalls
chains or
feather earrings however they dress is
not to be joked about
i pity the fool that judges another
man's clothing
i'm sorry i judge your clothing it's
okay
[Music]
hey scout there's a man over there who
said he'll give us candy if we get in
his van
i don't know if that's a good idea timmy
oh
what are you afraid of is it because you
have a stupid name like scout
hey whoa mr t again
never make fun of a person's name your
mama gave you that name
or you made it up for business purposes
either way
it's personal i'll pity the fool to make
fun of another man's name
mr t is a cool name it's a cool name mr
t
[Music]
hey scout want to do some drugs aren't
drugs bad
i don't know
if you're afraid of drugs we could drink
a bunch of alcohol
yum that sounds good
well guess what your hair is stupid
never make fun of another person's hair
hey mr t a person's hair is the artwork
that they present to the heavens
it's just like i've been saying
[Music]
a is
r is for the real mean jokes you make
and the hurtful little pack shots that
you take
and for your information it's not even a
haircut
it's a rare form of male pattern
baldness
your fools
[Music]
wow
oh
[Music]
huh did you hear that
must have been nothing
[Music]
back patio is clear
nice
[Music]
now it's my turn to play
ah
[Music]
carol
i thought i killed you the first time
i promised i will not make your same
mistake twice
[Music]
you are a good cop mr cheese but a lousy
fighter
[Music]
oh
snap indeed
teague you saved my life
no carol you saved mine
[Music]
oh
it's just
[Music]
hi i'm ray parker jr writer and
performer
of the academy award-nominated hit
single
ghostbusters from the major motion
picture
ghostbusters but that's just one song
i've written so many other major motion
picture theme songs
and submitted them throughout the year
now they're available
and together for one specially priced
compilation
songs like you tried to play the game
but it's driving you insane
jumanji danger in the jungle
jumanji there's lying in my house
come on mr computer throw me a bone
i said lawn mower man get up off of my
lawn
when armageddon is near you better get
out of here
[Music]
i ain't afraid to know destroyed watch
out behind you that's trying to find you
pelican
briefs it's getting legal y'all
these songs have only been heard by the
highest level of industry decision
makers
but now you can feel like a hollywood
executive
in your own home i see your face off
that guy walking around it's a face off
that ain't even your face pass another
christ
get me down off for this cross passing
off the christ
you know my daddy is the boss to serve
me
yeah that's not even a word
now there's a whole lot of kinky that
that room is stinky
50 shades of grey all right white people
who's a slave i'm not a slave
oh 12 years i say
what
[Music]
there's one thing i know is that
persistence
makes perfection sure hollywood missed
out
but that doesn't mean you have to down
in the basement what's going on
it's uh there's a kid and a nazi down
there
[Music]
order now to receive your free copy of
bobby sings the twos
theme songs to sequels that were never
made
oh hey guys gremlins too
i'm telling you this movie should write
itself
the first one was a classic this should
be pretty straightforward basically
all we're doing is maintaining the
integrity of the original picture
we want to do all the stuff with the
water and the
uh can we help you i'm sorry
let me introduce myself hi y'all
my name is star magic jackson jr i'm the
hollywood sql doctor so
studio just brings me in to oversee
things when they about to drop a deuce
so that's why i'm here but don't mind me
i'm just gonna be over here y'all do
your thing
it's your movie okay
uh let's brainstorm adam uh if it's
gonna take place in an office building i
was thinking what if
uh gizmo gets wet from a water cooler
this time okay hold on a second
i'm sorry i'm gonna have to step in here
just one second sweetheart so what's
wrong with y'all
y'all looking like a bunch of sad sacks
this
is g2 people we write in gremlins too it
should be a party
with pizza and anchovies pineapple just
come on lift up the spirits look okay
i'm gonna put a little bit of spice
into the mixture here what if we did
this everybody here
gets to design their own gremlin um
i don't see that the uh the gremlin
design is broken
it's called brainstorming i'm brain
drizzling sweet pea
okay shut your mouth for a second look
here's the thing
none of this is finals so you mean like
what if there was like a brainy grandma
a brainy gremlin
you talking about a gremlin with glasses
who could talk and sing new york new
york
that's brilliant it's in the movie done
whoa whoa you said that nothing was
final that was before i heard the words
brainy and gremlin in the same sentence
together it's done
i love it it's in the movie next what
about a uh
spider gremlin you mean a gremlin with
eight legs and a thorax just catching
pretty ladies in a web in an office
building oh my god it's in the movie i
love it
next what about a bat gremlin you mean a
gremlin with leathery wings just flying
around flip-flopping bust through a wall
make a perfect bat symbol in the wall
get outside getting some wet concrete
jump up on a building that just dry in
place like a gargoyle wherever we are
cooking with gas now i love it it's in
the movie next
could there be a female gremlin lipstick
boobies you have me in little
gremlin but jj i love it so much that
it's not only in the movie but it's
definitely
in the movie there's no backseats on
that one no penny taxi
yes yes yes in the movie done that's why
we need a woman in the writer's room
next
i don't know a googly-eyed gremlin
but you do know because you talking
about a gremlin whose sole purpose
in this film it's just that he looks
stupid
yes it can be in the movie and it ends
in the movie
done next what about you silver fox oh
electricity gremlin
you just said noun and gremlin like you
playing madness you're just like a child
you have the brain of a child
you do not have a high iq but you have
hats and you came
up with a gremlin that's just made out
of bolts that are zigzagging all over
the room and it's done completely in
animation
you're a crazy person and your idea's in
the movie done
next uh can we put the hulkster in it
what
[Music]
you talking about putting hulk hogan
professional wrestler turned actor
turned cultural icon in the movie
where he break the fourth wall of the
movie he's in by
talking to the audience you sir
a raging psychopath don't let this town
take that away from you
that's it i don't even care anymore we
got the hulkster in this so it's
done
i don't have any more time so let me
just recap right now it's brainy
gremlins spider gremlin back gremlin
lady gremlin googly eyed gremlin
electricity gremlin hulk hogan's gonna
be in the picture i'm gonna throw in a
grandma myself
vegetable gremlin just write it up i'm
having so much fun thank you
it's all gonna be in the actual film now
i gotta go put some cowboys and back to
the future three
sayonara y'all
no okay you guys know that none of that
is gonna be in the actual movie
[Music]
oh